boycrush.com 2008-02-20

# BoyCrush.com - Twink Hardcore Action

**Privacy Policy**

Effective on: Tuesday August 2nd, 2005

**Coverage**

This policy covers how BoyCrush.com treats personal information that it collects and receives. This includes information related to present and prior use of BoyCrush.com's services. Personal information refers to any information about you that is personally identifiable and not publicly available such as your name, address, email address, phone number or browsing habits.

This policy does not apply to affiliated companies that BoyCrush.com does not own or control. This policy also does not apply to people BoyCrush.com does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection**

BoyCrush.com collects aggregate usage and access information for every accessible page on BoyCrush.com. This may include pictures and links that users click on and any files they download.

BoyCrush.com also receives and records information in our server logs provided by your browser such as your IP address, cookie information, and the requested page.

BoyCrush.com uses this information to: customize the website to the specific user, improve our services, contact you, conduct research on usage and better understand customer habits.

**Third Parties**

Understanding our customers is a large portion of our business and we give protecting customer data a priority. We employ or partner with other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf. For instance, we partner with a credit card processor to process payments online. We share necessary information with these entities so they may perform the jobs that have been requested, but they may not use this information for any other purpose. We do not sell personal information to any third party.

**Security**

We use industry-standard practices for protecting customer data. Employees are limited to the amount of information they will receive about a customer, unless they perform a duty that requires personally identifiable information. They may use this information solely for the purpose of performing this duty and are required to destroy any notes, or copies of personal information when the duty is complete. Our servers are located behind a "firewall" in a secure loaction, and may only be acessed by a secure login. Please note that our servers are operated in a third party colocation facility, and while they do not have direct acess to our records, their actions are out of our control.

**Choice**

If at any time you wish to no longer recieve communications from our company you may opt-out by simply emailing us directly at Support@BoyCrush.com.

**Modifications**

BoyCrush.com reserves the right to change and update this policy by posting it online. Changes to this policy are effective when they are posted and it is your responsibility to periodicly check this policy so you are aware of any revisions to which you are bound.

**External Links**

This Site contains links to other sites. BoyCrush.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
